확실해? 모아관계는 영장류 심리학의 기본이야
Are you sure? The infant-mother pair-bond
그럼 그렇지
Oh, there it is.
넌 항상 원숭이 타령이야
It always comes back to monkeys with you.
원숭이, 원숭이, 원숭이
Just monkeys, monkeys, monkeys.
쉘든, 우리는 동물이야
Sheldon, we're all animals.
네가 어떤 면으로는 특별하기도 한데
And granted, there are aspects of you that are extraordinary,
감정이랑 관계에서는
but when it comes to emotions and relationships,
누구나 다 똑같아
you're just like everybody else.
내가 감정적으로 겪는 문제들이
Are you trying to suggest that my emotional problems
바보랑 같은 수준이라는 거야?
are no different than those of a stupid person?
어떤 연구에 의하면
Actually, some research indicates
지적 능력이 낮은 사람들이 감정을 더 잘 다스린대
that by not overthinking,